cspan.org 2019-12-15

# Privacy | C-SPAN.org

## C-SPAN'S Online Privacy Policy

C-SPAN is sensitive to the privacy concerns of the visitors to all of its websites and to users of its apps. The websites, which can be reached through the domain www.c-span.org, are operated by National Cable Satellite Corporation, d/b/a C-SPAN ("NCSC" or "C-SPAN" or "we" or "our" or "us"). This Privacy Policy applies to all of our websites except The C-SPAN Store site, which collects credit card and other information from users and the C‑SPAN Radio app. The privacy policy for the C‑SPAN Radio app is below.

This policy applies to all the other sites that can be reached from www.c-span.org. It describes the types of information collected from you, what we do with it, with whom we share it and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing us any personal data. **Your use of this site signifies your agreement to its terms**.

### Personally Identifying Information:

Personally Identifying Information ("Personal Data") is any information that can be used to identify a specific individual. It includes information such as your name, email address, home address, photograph, and phone number. We do not collect Personal Data from you unless you volunteer it. For example, when you create a MyC-SPAN account you are asked for an email address, a username, and your first and last name. You may also choose to provide a photograph and some background information. If you use the "add to my calendar" feature of MyC-SPAN account, you will make certain program choices linked to you. All of this is Personal Data that we retain.

Our agents and contractors who have access to your Personal Data are required by us to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing on our behalf. 

When you verify your cable or satellite subscription to get online access to the live streams of C-SPAN, C-SPAN2 and C-SPAN3 you are also providing Personal Data to your cable company, satellite company or other distributor. Your distributor may use your Personal Data for its own purposes as described in its privacy policy.

### Our Use of Your Personal Data:

We will use your Personal Data for the purposes for which it was provided. For example, if you provide Personal Data to create a MyC-SPAN account, we will use it to provide you with that service. We will not use your Personal Data for any other purpose. For example, we will not give it to others for advertising purposes. We will not give it to any of our affiliates. We will retain it indefinitely. However, if you choose to delete your MyC-SPAN account, we will delete your Personal Data from our records. 

### Correction and Deletion:

If you would like to review, correct or change the Personal Data that you provided us when you created a MyC-SPAN account, you may do so by going to the Edit Your MyC-SPAN Profile page and click on "edit my account." If you would like to delete your account, you can do so on the same page by clicking the Delete My Account button.

### MyC-SPAN Accounts:

  * #### 'Public' or 'Private':

You have the option to create a MyC-SPAN account that is either 'public' or 'private.' If your account is 'public' your username (and photograph, if you provide one) may be listed on other website pages along with your video clip choices. If your account is 'private' only your video clip choices will appear without any connection to you personally. If you do not select either 'public' or 'private' in setting up your account, it will be 'private.'

  * #### Aggregated Anonymous Data:

We may also use Personal Data in aggregate form for purposes of research or analysis. In order to better understand and serve users we may conduct research on user demographics, interests and behavior based on Personal Data we gather. Although this aggregated data may be based in part on Personal Data, it does not identify you personally. We may also use aggregated data collected from the website for site administration, promotional purposes, and we may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes. For example, IP addresses are used for system administration and to provide aggregated data to third parties about the volume of use on the website.

  * #### Aggregated and Anonymous Information and "Cookies":

We may use "cookies" and similar tools to relate your use of c-span.org and aggregated data to your Personal Data. If any aggregated data is linked with Personal Data, the linked aggregated data will then be treated as Personal Data. A cookie is a small data file written to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit our site. Cookies allow us to measure traffic activity and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your password or enabling us to send you weekly C-SPAN Alerts. Regardless, no information gathered through the use of cookies will be shared with any unaffiliated third parties. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent, but it is possible that some parts of the website will not function properly if you do so.

### The C‑SPAN Radio App

If you download the C-SPAN Radio app, you will be asked if you want to receive push notifications from us. If you choose to receive them you will occasionally receive alerts informing you of radio programs that you may be interested in. The C‑SPAN Radio app incorporates third party software, and may collect information about your personal device, including its advertising identifier (which is Personal Data). The software provider is neither a contractor nor an agent of C‑SPAN.

### Disclosure to Others:

We may disclose Personal Data without providing you with a choice under the following limited circumstances to: (1) protect the legal rights, privacy or safety of NCSC or its subsidiaries, affiliates or its or their employees, agents and contractors; (2) protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites or other properties; (3) protect against fraud or other illegal activity or for risk management purposes; (4) respond to inquiries or requests from public authorities; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; (6) or comply with the law or legal process.

_This Policy Statement is made in the name of National Cable Satellite Corporation and is effective as of January 1, 2014 and will not be changed without notifying users by means of a revised statement at this website. This statement does not create an agreement between the NCSC and users and, as such, does not create any legal rights for any party. NCSC is the non-profit and tax-exempt educational corporation that owns and operates C-SPAN, C-SPAN2, C-SPAN3, WCSP-FM, C SPAN.org, and related websites. The c-span.org website is operated in and controlled from the United States of America._
